Guide to the Leather bound books,1808-1847.
Leather bound books,1808-1847
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Leather bound books, 1808-1847.
8008
3 cubic ft.
Books
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Multi-volume sets in leather bindings. Textbooks and standard reference works on the subjects of law and mathematics.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Multi-volume sets in leather bindings. Textbooks and standard reference works on the subjects of law and mathematics.
SUBJECTS
Subjects:
Law. Textbooks; Mathematics. Textbooks.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Archbold, John Frederick. The practice of the Court of King's bench in personal actions, and ejectment. New York, Gould, 1823. v.1-2 (Box 1)
- Bacon, Matthew. A new abridgement of the law. Phildelphia, Farrand and Nicholas, 1811. v.2-7 (Box 1)
- Ballantine, William. A treatise on the statute of limitations. Albany, Packard and Co., 1829 (Box 1)
- Bridgman, Richard Whalley. A synthesis of the rules and principles of the law of nisi prius,... New York, Franklin Co., 1811 (Box 1)
- Buttmann, Philip. Greek grammar for the use of schools. Boston, Cummings, Hilliard and Co., 1826 (Box 1)
- Chitty, Joseph. A practical treatise on bills of exchange, checks on bankers, promissory notes, bankers' cash notes, and bank notes. Georgetown, Richards, 1817 (Box 1)
- Chitty, Joseph. A practical treatise on the law of nations, relative to the legal effect of war on the commerce of belligerents and neutrals... Boston, Bradford and Read, 1812 (Box 1)
- Clerke, Thomas W. A practical elementary digest of the reported cases in the Supreme Court of Judicature. New York, Gould, Banks & Co., 1841. 2d edition. 2 v. in 3 (Box 2)
- Cowen, Sidney J. A treatise on the civil jurisdiction of justices of the peace in the state of New York. Albany, Gould & Co., 1841. Pt. 1-2 (Box 2)
- Flint, Abel. A system of geometry and trigonometry together with a treatise on surveying,... 4th ed., Hartford, Cooke & Hale, 1818 (Box 2)
- Fonblanque, John. A treatise of equity with the addition of marginal references and notes. Philadelphia, Small, 1820. v.1-2 (Box 2)
- Graham, David. A treatis on the practice of the Supreme Court of the State of New York. 2d ed. New York, Gould, Banks & Co., 1836 (Box 2)
- Hall, John E. American law journal and miscellaneous repertory. Baltimore, Nicklin and Co., 1809-1810. v.2-3 (Box 2)
- Hammond, Anthony. A practical treatise on parties to actions and proceedings civil and criminal and of rights and liabilities... Exeter, N.H., G. Lamson, 1822 (Box 2)
- Hoffman, David. Legal outlines, being the substance of a course of lectures now delivering in the University of Maryland. Baltimore, E.J. Coale, 1829. v.1 only (Box 2)
- Horace. Poemata. Novi Eboraci, G.&C.&H. Carvill, 1830 (Box 2)
- Johnson, William. A digest of the cases decided and reported in the Supreme Court of Judicature and the court for the correction of errors, in the State of New York from Jan. 1799 to Oct. 1813... Albany, E.F. Backus, 1815. Pt. 1-2 (Box 3)
- Lawes, Edward. An elementary treatise on pleading in civil actions. 1st Amer. Ed from 1st London ed. Portsmouth, N.H., Thomas and Tappan, 1808 (Box 3)
- Legendre, A. M. Elements of geometry and trigonometry... Revised and altered, New York, J. Ryan, 1828 (Box 3)
- Lube, D. G. An analysis of the principles of equity pleading, containing a compendium of the practice of the high court of chancery and the foundation of its rules. 1st Amer. From last London ed., New York, Gould, Banks & Co., 1840 (Box 3)
- New York State. The revised statutes of the State of New York. 3rd ed., Albany, W.C. Little and Co., 1846 v.1-3 (Box 3)
- New York State. Rules of practice of the Supreme Court of the State of New York, at law and in equity, as established by the court at July term, 1847. Albany, Gould, Banks & Gould, 1847 (Box 3)
- Playfair, John. Elements of geometry, containing the first six books of Euclid. Last London ed., enlarged. New York, Duyckinck, Long, etc., 1828 (Box 3)
- Roberts, William. A treatise on the law of wills and codicils. 1st Amer. From the last London ed, improved..., Exeter, N.H., G. Lamson, 1823. v. 1-2 (Box 3)